<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="Stylesheet/Vector_Attributes.xsl"?>
<Vector_Attributes
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xmlns="http://www.opengis.net/cdb/1.0/Vector_Attributes"
  xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.opengis.net/cdb/1.0/Vector_Attributes http://schemas.opengis.net/cdb/1.0/Vector_Attributes.xsd"
  version="3.2">

  <Attributes>
  
    <Attribute code="1" symbol="AEAC" deprecated="true">
      <Name>ATARS Extended Attribute Code</Name>
      <Description>
        A unique numeric identifier that points to the entry number of the ATARS Extended Attribution file for the current dataset.
        This entry is provided for legacy database generation facility considerations only; CDB-compliant devices are not required to read and interpret this field.
        The ATARS Extended Attribution file should be located in the same directory as the instance-level attribution file.
        An empty AEAC field (i.e., null string) is allowed.
        Refer to Section 3.6.6, Tiled Datasets Folder Hierarchical Organization for the file naming conventions of vector datasets.
        NOTE: The AEAC is attribute is deprecated as a result of the more comprehensive Extended-level attribution schema introduced in version 3.1 of the CDB Specification.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Supported</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="2" symbol="AHGT">
      <Name>Absolute Height Flag</Name>
      <Description>
        Indicates how to interpret the Z component of a vertex.
        If AHGT is true, the feature is positioned to the value specified by the Z component (Absolute Terrain Altitude), irrelevant of the terrain elevation dataset.
        If AHGT is false or not present, the feature is positioned to the value specified by the underlying terrain offset by the Z component value.
        Refer to section 5.6.1.1, ShapeFile Type Usage and Conventions for more details.
        AHGT can be present only in datasets using PointZ, PolylineZ, PolygonZ and MultiPointZ Shape types.
        AHGT should not be present for all other Shape types or must be ignored otherwise.
        Refer to Appendix A – "How to Interpret the AHGT, HGT, BSR, BBH, and Z Attributes" for additional usage guidelines.
        NOTE: It is recommended that the AHGT flag be set to false because it facilitates the creation of CDB datasets that are independent of each others.
        When the Z coordinate (altitude) of a feature is relative to the ground, the terrain elevation dataset can be updated without the need to recompute the altitude of the feature.
        CAUTION: When the AHGT flag is set to true, the feature will be at a fixed WGS-84 elevation independently of the terrain LOD selected by the client-device.
        As a result, there is no guarantee that the feature (and its modeled representation) will remain above the terrain skin across all terrain LODs.
        RECOMMENDATION: Limit the use of AHGT=TRUE to data whose source is inherently absolute.
        Such source data include geodetic marks or survey marks that provide a known position in terms of latitude, longitude, and altitude.
        Good examples of such markers are boundary markers between countries.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Not Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Boolean</Type>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="3" symbol="AO1">
      <Name>Angle of Orientation with greater than 1 degree resolution</Name>
      <Description>
        The angular distance measured from true north (0 deg) clockwise to the major (Y) axis of the feature.
        If the feature is square, the axis 0 through 89.999 deg shall be recorded.
        If the feature is circular, 360.000 deg shall be recorded.
        Recommended Usage. CDB readers should default to a value of 0.000 if AO1 is missing.
        Applicable to Point, Light Point, Moving Model Location and Figure Point features.
        When used in conjunction with the PowerLine dataset, AO1 corresponds to the orientation of the Y-axis of the modeled pylon.
        The modeled pylon should be oriented (in its local Cartesian space) so that the wires nominally attach along the Y-axis.
        Refer to Appendix A – “Creating a 3D Model for a Powerline Pylon” for additional usage guidelines.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>3.3</Precision>
        <Range interval="Right-Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>360</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>2</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
  
    <Attribute code="4" symbol="APFN" deprecated="true">
      <Name>Airport Feature Name</Name>
      <Description>...</Description>
      <Level>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
        <Extended>Preferred</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>24</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="5" symbol="APID">
      <Name>AirPort ID</Name>
      <Description>
        A unique alphanumeric identifier that points to a record in the NavData Airport or Heliport dataset (i.e., a link to the Airport or the Heliport description in the NavData dataset).
        This ID is the value of the field Ident of the Airport or Heliport dataset.
        Note that all of the lights located in list-organized datasets that are associated with the operation of an airport (including runway lights and lighting systems) are required to reference an airport or heliport in the NavData dataset.
        All man-made features associated with an airport or heliport must be assigned an APID attribute; the APID attribute is not required for features unrelated to airports or heliports.
        Usage Note: Recommended for all Airport Light Points and airport-related i2DModels (such as runway/taxiway/apron surfaces, and markings).
        Failure to appropriately tag airport culture with APID attribute will result in reduced control of airport-related culture by simulator.
        Optional for Location Points, Environmental Light Points, and Moving Model Location features that fall within the confines of an airport and for which control of the feature is desirable.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>6</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
  
    <Attribute code="6" symbol="BBH">
      <Name>Bounding Box Height</Name>
      <Description>
        The Height/Width/Length of the Bounding Box of the 3D model associated with a point feature.
        It is the dimension of the box centered at the model origin and that bounds the portion of the model above its XY plane,
        including the envelopes of all articulated parts.
        BBH refers to height of the box above the XY plane of the model,
        BBW refers to the width of the box along the X-axis,
        and BBL refers to the length of the box along the Y-axis.
        Note that for 3D models used as cultural features, the XY plane of the model corresponds to its ground reference plane.
        The value of BBH, BBW and BBL should be accounted for by client-devices (in combination with other information)
        to determine the appropriate distance at which the model should be paged-in, rendered or processed.
        BBH, BBW and BBL are usually generated through database authoring tool automation.
        Optional on features for which a MODL has been assigned.
        When missing, CDB readers should default BBH to the value of BSR, and BBW and BBL to twice the value of BSR.
        The dimension of the bounding box is intrinsic to the model and identical for all LOD representations.
        Refer to Appendix A – "How to Interpret the AHGT, HGT, BSR, BBH, and Z Attributes" for additional usage guidelines.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>5.3</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100000</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>1</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="7" symbol="BBW">
      <Name>Bounding Box Width</Name>
      <Description>
        The width of a feature.
        See BBH for a complete description.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>5.3</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100000</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>1</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
        
    <Attribute code="8" symbol="BBL">
      <Name>Bounding Box Length</Name>
      <Description>
        The length of a feature.
        See BBH for a complete description.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>5.3</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100000</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>1</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>

    <Attribute code="9" symbol="BOTY">
      <Name>Boundary Type</Name>
      <Description>
        A value that uniquely attributes a boundary according to the enumerators found here.
        Usage Note: Optional. See table 5-29 for a list of accepted values.
        Can be used only with Boundary Point, Lineal or Areal Feature Datasets (which are part of the Geopolitical Datasets)
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="10" symbol="BSR">
      <Name>Bounding Sphere Radius</Name>
      <Description>
        The radius of a feature.
        In the case where a feature references an associated 3D model,
        it is the radius of the hemisphere centered at the model origin and that bounds the portion of the model above its XY plane,
        including the envelopes of all articulated parts.
        Note that for 3D models used as cultural features, the XY plane of the model corresponds to its ground reference plane.
        The value of BSR should be accounted for by client-devices (in combination with other information)
        to determine the appropriate distance at which the model should be paged-in, rendered or processed.
        When the feature does not reference a 3D model, BSR is the radius of the abstract point representing the feature (e.g., a city).
        Usage Note:
        Mandatory for features for which a MODL has been assigned, but optional for geopolitical point features.
        The dimension of the bounding sphere is intrinsic to the model and identical for all LOD representations.
        Refer to Appendix A – "How to Interpret the AHGT, HGT, BSR, BBH, and Z Attributes" for additional usage guidelines.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>5.3</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100000</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>1</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="11" symbol="CEAI">
      <Name>CDB Extended Attribute Index</Name>
      <Description>
        An index that points to a row entry of a CDB Extended Attribution file for the current dataset.
        This entry permits users to store an index to a link list set of CDB-specific attributes.
        CDB-compliant devices must be capable of reading and interpreting this field.
        Usage of this attribution is not portable to other simulators because it falls outside of the documented CDB attribution scheme.
        The CDB Extended Attribution file should be located in the same directory as the instance-level attribution file.
        An empty CEAI attribute is allowed. Note that the first entry in the CDB Extended Attribution file has an index of 1.
        Usage Note: Optional. Use when CDB extended attribution is required. A “blank” or a value of 0 indicates that there are no CDB Extended attributes.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Not Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>1</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="12" symbol="CEAC" deprecated="true">
      <Name>CDB Extended Attribute Code</Name>
      <Description>
        A unique numeric identifier that points to the entry number of a CDB Extended Attribution file for the current dataset.
        This entry permits users to store a link to a set of CDB-specific attributes beyond those explicitly supported by the current version of this Specification.
        CDB-compliant devices may optionally read and interpret this field due to program requirements that cannot be supported by the current version of the CDB.
        Usage of this attribution is not portable to other simulators because it falls outside of the documented CDB attribution scheme.
        The CDB Extended Attribution file should be located in the same directory as the instance-level attribution file.
        An empty CEAC field is allowed.
        Refer to Section 3.6.6, Tiled Datasets Folder Hierarchical Organization for the file naming conventions of vector datasets.
        NOTE: The CEAC attribute is deprecated as a result of the more comprehensive Extended-level attribution schema introduced in version 3.1 of the CDB Specification.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Deprecated</Instance>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="13" symbol="CMIX">
      <Name>Composite Material Index</Name>
      <Description>
        Index into the Composite Material Table is used to determine the Base Materials composition of the associated feature.
        Refer to Section 2.5, Material Naming Conventions for a description on material naming conventions.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="14" symbol="CNAM">
      <Name>Class Name</Name>
      <Description>
        A name that represents the Attribution Class.
        The class-level attribution schema is described in Section 5.6.1.2.7.2, Class-level Schema.
        Attributes are referenced via this classname.
        The classname is used as the primary key to perform searches within the Dataset Class Attribute file.
        Each row of a class-level *.dbf ShapeFile must have a valid CNAM entry; the CNAM must be unique within the file.
        Each row of an instance-level *.dbf can optionally use the CNAM to refer to class attributes; blank indicates “no class attribute”.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Supported</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Not Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>32</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="67" symbol="DAMA">
      <Name>Damage Level</Name>
      <Description>
        Represents the level of damage of the feature and its model.
        The level is expressed as a percentage where 0% means no damage at all and 100% means fully damaged and completely destroyed.
        In the case of network datasets, the level of damage shall be interpreted as a measure of the incapacity of the feature to perform its function.
        For instance, a road network whose damage level is 75% tells the client that it is only able to perform 25% of its intended function.
        As a result, a client may decide that it cannot use the road network while another client may continue to do so.
        
        In the context of HLA/DIS, the concept of DAMA maps directly to the concepts of Damage State for which the standards define 4 states named No Damage, Slight Damage, Moderate Damage, and Destroyed.
        The Specification suggests the following mapping between CDB and HLA/DIS.
        
        From CDB to HLA/DIS,
        if DAMA &lt; 25 then State = No Damage;
        else if DAMA &lt; 50 then State = Slight Damage;
        else if DAMA &lt; 75 then State = Moderate Damage;
        else State = Destroyed.
        
        From HLA/DIS to CDB,
        if State = Destroyed then DAMA = 100;
        else if State = Moderate Damage then DAMA = 66;
        else if State = Slight Damage then DAMA = 33;
        else DAMA = 0.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>7</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="15" symbol="DEAC" deprecated="true">
      <Name>DIGEST Extended Attribute Code</Name>
      <Description>
        A unique numeric identifier that points to the entry number of the DIGEST Extended Attribution file for the current dataset.
        This entry is provided for legacy database generation facility considerations only; it provides a means for the CDB to act as a repository for legacy DIGEST attribution.
        CDB-compliant devices are not required to read and interpret this field.
        The DIGEST Extended Attribution file should be located in the same directory as the instance-level attribution file.
        An empty DEAC field (i.e., null string) is allowed.
        Refer to Section 3.6.6, Tiled Datasets Folder Hierarchical OrganizationDirectory for the file naming conventions of vector datasets.
        Usage Note: Optional. Use when DIGEST extended attribution is required.
        NOTE: The DEAC attribute is deprecated as a result of the more comprehensive Extended-level attribution schema introduced in version 3.1 of the CDB Specification.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Deprecated</Instance>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="16" symbol="DEP">
      <Name>Depth below Surface Level</Name>
      <Description>
        Distance measured from the highest point at surface level to the lowest point of the feature below the surface.
        Recorded values are positive numbers.
        In the case of hydrographic lineal feature, DEPth refers to the depth of rivers, lakes, etc.
        This data is typically used by client-device that needs to determine whether a waterway is navigable by ships/boats with a specific draw.
        Usage Note: Mandatory. Applicable to lineal features with depth, especially for HydrographyNetwork Dataset features.
        Not applicable to features that are intrinsically above ground.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>5.3</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100000</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="17" symbol="DIR">
      <Name>Directivity</Name>
      <Description>
        The side or sides of a feature that has the greatest reflectivity potential.
        This data is typically needed for Radar simulation.
        DIR is used solely for lineal features in accordance to DFAD conventions.
        Value of 1 means Uni-directional, 2 means Bi-directional, and 3 means Omni-directional.
        If DIR is not equal to 3, then AO1 is the angular distance measured from true north (0 deg) clockwise to the reflective side of the feature.
        Usage Note: Recommended for lineal features. If absent, client-devices are required to default to a value of 3 – Omni-directional.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="18" symbol="DML">
      <Name>Density Measure (% light cover)</Name>
      <Description>
        Percentage light coverage at night (expressed as a percentage) within the area of delimited by an areal feature.
        Usage Note: Recommended. Applies to Geopolitical Dataset areal features that delineate inhabited areas.
        If this field is absent, client-devices shall assume 0%.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>7</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="19" symbol="DMR">
      <Name>Density Measure (% roof cover)</Name>
      <Description>
        Roof cover measure by percent within area of feature.
        Usage Note: Recommended for Areal features.
        If absent, client-devices shall assume 0%.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>7</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="20" symbol="DMS">
      <Name>Density Measure (structure count)</Name>
      <Description>
        Number of man-made, habitable structures per square kilometer.
        Usage Note: Recommended for Areal features. If absent, client-devices shall assume 0.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100000</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="21" symbol="DMT">
      <Name>Density Measure (% tree/canopy cover)</Name>
      <Description>
        Roof cover measure by percent within area of feature.
        Usage Note: Recommended for Areal features. If absent, client-devices shall assume 0%.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>7</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="22" symbol="EJID">
      <Name>End Junction ID</Name>
      <Description>
        Unique Identification Number that is used to virtually connect the end point of a lineal to another point, lineal or areal feature.
        Lineal features stored in the same shape file having the same SJID or EJID are connected.
        Lineal features stored in different shape files having the same SJID or EJID as the JID listed in the corresponding tile 2D relationship file (*.dbf) are connected.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for all features belonging to Topological Network Datasets.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="23" symbol="FACC">
      <Name>Feature Attribute Classification Code</Name>
      <Description>
        This code used to distinguish and categorize features within a dataset.
        The enumerated codes are in accordance to DIGEST 2.1.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>5</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="24" symbol="FSC">
      <Name>FACC Sub Code</Name>
      <Description>
        This code, in conjunction with the FACC is used to distinguish and categorize features within a dataset.
        The enumerated codes are in accordance to Appendix N.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="25" symbol="GAID">
      <Name>Gate AirPort ID</Name>
      <Description>
        A unique alphanumeric identifier (for the airport in question) that points to the IDENT attribute name within the NavData Gate dataset (i.e., a link to the Gate description in the NavData dataset).
        This ID is the value of the Gate Identifier of the Gate dataset and can be used to extract additional information such as the gate position and bearing.
        Usage Note: Recommended and Optional usages are per Table 5-37: Allocation of CDB Attributes to Datasets.
        Typically used (but not limited to) for models such as docking systems, marshallers and other models that are logically associated with a Terminal gate and that require some level of control by the simulation application.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>6</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>

    <Attribute code="26" symbol="GEAI">
      <Name>Geomatics Extended Attribute Index</Name>
      <Description>
        An index that points to a row entry of a Geomatics Extended Attribution file for the current dataset.
        This entry permits users to store an index to a link list set of Geomatics-specific attributes.
        CDB-compliant devices are not mandated to read and interpret this field.
        Usage of this attribution is not portable to other simulators because it falls outside of the documented CDB attribution scheme.
        The Geomatics Extended Attribution file should be located in the same directory as the instance-level attribution file.
        An empty GEAI attribute is allowed.
        Note that the first entry in the Geomatics Extended Attribution file has an index of 1.
        Usage Note: Optional. Use when Geomatics extended attribution is required.
        A “blank” or a value of 0 indicates that there are no Geomatics Extended attributes.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Not Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>1</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="27" symbol="HGT">
      <Name>Height above surface level</Name>
      <Description>
        Distance measured from the lowest point of the base at ground (non-floating objects) or water level (floating objects downhill side/downstream side) to the tallest point of the feature above the surface.
        Recorded values are positive numbers.
        In the case of roads and railroads, HGT corresponds to the elevation of the road/railroad wrt terrain in its immediate vicinity.
        Usage Note: Mandatory on all Point and Figure Point features for which a MODL has been assigned.
        Recommended on Lineal features except coastline (coastlines are assumed to be zero).
        Optional for Airport and Environmental Light Points.
        Recommended on all areals features.
        Refer to Appendix A – "How to Interpret the AHGT, HGT, BSR, BBH, and Z Attributes" for additional usage guidelines.
        Default: Value must be provided for Point and Figure Point features. For the lineal and areal features, a default value of 0.00 should be used.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>4.2</Precision>
        <Range interval="Right-Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>10000</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>1</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="28" symbol="JID">
      <Name>Junction ID</Name>
      <Description>
        Unique Identification Number that is used to virtually connect a point or an areal feature to another point, lineal or areal feature.
        Features stored in the same shape file having the same JID are connected.
        Features stored in different shape files having the same JID as the JID listed in the corresponding tile 2D relationship file (*.dbf) are connected.
        When JID is associated to an areal feature, it necessarily connects to the first point of the areal feature.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for all features belonging to Topological Network Datasets.
        Attribute is used in 2D relationship file.
        Attribute is stored as a character string representing an unsigned 64-bit number, and requires conversion back into numerical representation by client reader.
        This is due to the 32-bit limitation on integer values within dbf files.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="29" symbol="LACC">
      <Name>Location Accuracy</Name>
      <Description>
        A precision value used to quantify the relative precision of the Location point representing the specific GeoPolitical Location.
        Usage Note: Optional. See Table 5-30: Location Accuracy Enumeration Values for a list of accepted values.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="30" symbol="LENL">
      <Name>Length of Lineal</Name>
      <Description>
        The length of a lineal.
        If the feature has been clipped to a tile boundary, the length still gives the initial full length of the object prior to the clipping operation,
        and if it belonged to a topological network, LENL will represent the distance between the two closest junction points encompassing this lineal segment.
        Note the Length attribute is not used to define a bounding sphere associated to an object, but rather to provide a weight to the relative length of the
        lineal as compared to others.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for all networked lineal features. Length computation should be account for the earth’s curvature.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="31" symbol="LMIX" deprecated="true">
      <Name>Light Material Index</Name>
      <Description>
        Index into the Composite Material Table that is used to determine the Light Material composition of the associated city illumination.
        Represent the predominant material characterizing the major light attributes of a populated area.
        Refer to Section 2.5, Material Naming Conventions for a description on material naming conventions.
        Usage Note: Optional. Applicable to Geopolitical Dataset areal features that delineate inhabited areas.
        NOTE: The LMIX attribute is deprecated in version 3.1
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="32" symbol="LNAM">
      <Name>Location Name</Name>
      <Description>A name that corresponds to a GeoPolitical Location. Usage Note: Optional. Blank indicates "no name".</Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>32</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="33" symbol="LOTY">
      <Name>Location Type</Name>
      <Description>
        A value that uniquely attributes a location feature according to the enumerators found here.
        Enumeration per Table 5-31: Location Type Enumeration Values.
        Usage Note: Optional. Applicable to Geopolitical Dataset areal features. See table below for a list of accepted values.
        Can be used only with Location Point, Lineal or Areal Feature Datasets (which are part of the Geopolitical Datasets).
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="34" symbol="LPH">
      <Name>Light Phase</Name>
      <Description>
        Used for all light types that are periodic in nature (rotating, blink, flashing, etc).
        The value of LPH controls the phase of the light relative to all other lights that share the same LTYP.
        All other light characteristics, including frequency and duration are implicitly determined by the LTYP.
        Usage Note: Optional. In absence of a value, LPH defaults to a value of 0.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="35" symbol="LPN">
      <Name>Layer Priority Number</Name>
      <Description>
        A priority number that establishes the relative priority of overlapping features.
        LPN establishes the order (starting from 0 for lowest priority) by which overlapping features are processed by client-devices.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for terrain constraint features that overlap one another.
        For all other features, it is optional.
        LPN is derived from priority information stored and maintained by the authoring tools.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>32767</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="36" symbol="LTN">
      <Name>Lane/Track Number</Name>
      <Description>
        The number of lanes on a road, tracks on railroad, or conductors on powerlines, including both directions.
        Usage Note: Recommended for Road, RailRoad, and Powerline Network features. Optional for Hydrography Network features.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>99</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="37" symbol="LTYP">
      <Name>Light Type</Name>
      <Description>
        A unique code corresponding to a Light Type; Appendix E of this Specification provides the supported light types.
        The light types follow a hierarchical organization provided by the light type naming conventions described in Section 2.3, Light Naming.
        The Lights.xml file (located in CDB\Metadata directory of the CDB storage structure) establishes the correspondence between the LTYP code and the Light Type name.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for all Airport Light Point features, Environmental Light Point features.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>9999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="38" symbol="MLOD">
      <Name>Model Level Of Detail</Name>
      <Description>
        The level of detail of the 3D model associated with the point feature.
        When used in conjunction with MODL, the MLOD attribute indicates the LOD where the corresponding MODL is found.
        In this case, the value of MLOD can never be larger than the LOD of the Vector Tile-LOD that contains it.
        When used in the context of Airport and Environmental Light Point features, the value of MLOD, if present,
        indicates that this light point also exist in a 3D model found at the specified LOD.
        In such case, the value of MLOD is not constrained and can indicate any LOD.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>-10</Min>
          <Max>23</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="39" symbol="MMDC">
      <Name>Moving Model DIS Code</Name>
      <Description>
        A character string composed of the 7 fields of the DIS Entity Type
        separated by an underscore character (“_”) and formatted like this: 1_2_3_4_5_6_7
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>29</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="40" symbol="MODL">
      <Name>Model Name</Name>
      <Description>
        A string reference, the model name, which stands for the modeled geometry of a feature;
        in the case of buildings, this includes both its external shell and modeled interior.
        Usage Note: Needed for Point features, Road Figure Point features, Railroad Figure Point features, Pipeline Figure Point features and Hydrography Figure
        Point features that are modeled as OpenFlight or as RCS (Shape).
        MODL can also be used with Road Lineal features, Railroad Lineal features, Pipeline Lineal features and Hydrography Lineal and Areal features.
        Note that it is not permitted to specify a value for MODL simultaneously with a value for MMDC.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>32</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="41" symbol="MODT">
      <Name>Model Type</Name>
      <Description>
        A flag indicating whether the modeled feature is geo-typical, geo-specific or a Moving Model.
        Together, the MODT flag, the FACC-FSC, and the MODL model name or the MMDC produce a unique path
        to a directory within the CDB hierarchy and a unique filename within that directory.
        Usage Note: Needed for features that are modeled as OpenFlight or as RCS (Shape).
        "T" for geo-typical, "S" for geo-specific, "M" for Moving Model. Default value is "S" when not present.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>1</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="42" symbol="NCS1">
      <Name>Network Component Selector 1</Name>
      <Description>
        Code that is used to identify the component selector 1 file which contain the point, lineal, or areal feature that is virtually connected.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for Network datasets. Attribute is used in 2D relationship file.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>9999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="43" symbol="NCS2">
      <Name>Network Component Selector 2</Name>
      <Description>
        Code that is used to identify the component selector 2 file which contain the point, lineal, or areal feature that is virtually connected.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for Network datasets. Attribute is used in 2D relationship file.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>9999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="44" symbol="NDSC">
      <Name>Network Dataset Code</Name>
      <Description>
        Code that is used to identify the dataset code file which contain the point, lineal, or areal feature that is virtually connected.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for Network datasets. Attribute is used in 2D relationship file.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>9999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="45" symbol="NIS" deprecated="true">
      <Name>Number of Instances</Name>
      <Description>
        Number of instances found in the 3D model associated with the cultural point feature.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
        <Extended>Preferred</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="46" symbol="NIX" deprecated="true">
      <Name>Number of Indices</Name>
      <Description>
        Number of indices found in the 3D model associated with the cultural point feature.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
        <Extended>Preferred</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="47" symbol="NNL" deprecated="true">
      <Name>Number of Normals</Name>
      <Description>
        Number of normal vectors found in the 3D model associated with the cultural point feature.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
        <Extended>Preferred</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="48" symbol="NTC" deprecated="true">
      <Name>Number of Texture Coordinates</Name>
      <Description>
        Number of texture coordinates found in the 3D model associated with the cultural point feature.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
        <Extended>Preferred</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="49" symbol="NTX" deprecated="true">
      <Name>Number of Texels</Name>
      <Description>
        Number of texels found in the 3D model associated with the cultural point feature.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Class>Deprecated</Class>
        <Extended>Preferred</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="50" symbol="NVT">
      <Name>Number of Vertices</Name>
      <Description>
        Number of vertices of the 3D model associated with a point feature.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="51" symbol="POPD">
      <Name>Population Density</Name>
      <Description>
        The number of inhabitants per square kilometer.
        Applicable to Geopolitical features representing inhabited areas.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>99999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="52" symbol="POPT">
      <Name>Populated Place Type</Name>
      <Description>
        A value that uniquely represents the Populated Place Attribution Type.
        This attribute should be used in conjunction with the BOTY attribute when BOTY has an (enumerator) value of 13 which corresponds to "Populated Place".
        Usage Note: Optional. Applies to Geopolitical Dataset areal features that delineate inhabited areas. See table below for a list of accepted values.
        Enumeration per Table 5-32: Populated Place Type Enumeration Values.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="53" symbol="RTAI">
      <Name>Relative Tactical Importance</Name>
      <Description>
        Provides the Relative TActical Importance of moving models or cultural features relative to other features for the purpose of client-device
        scene/load management. A value of 100% corresponds to the highest importance; a value of 0% corresponds to the lowest importance.
        When confronted with otherwise identical objects that differ only wrt to their RelativeTActical Importance, client-devices should always discard features
        with lower importance before those of higher importance in the course of performing their scene / load management function. As a
        result, a value of zero gives complete freedom to client-devices to discard the feature as soon as the load of the client-device is
        exceeded. The effectiveness of scene / load management functions can be severely hampered if large quantities of features are assigned
        the same Relative TActical Importance by the modeler. In effect, if all models are assigned the same value, the client-devices have no
        means to distinguish tactically important objects from each other. Assigning a value of 1% to all objects is equivalent to assigning
        them all a value of 99%. Ideally, the assignment of tactical importance to features should be in accordance to a histogram
        similar to the one shown here. The shape of the curve is not critical, however the proportion of models tagged with a high importance
        compared to those with low importance is critical in achieving effective scene/load management schemes. It is illustrated here to
        show that few models should have an importance of 100 with progressively more models with lower importance. The assignment
        of the RTAI to each feature lends itself to database tools automation. For instance, RTAI could be based on a look-up function which
        factors the feature’s type (FACC or MMDC). The value of Relative TActical Importance should be accounted for by client-devices
        (in combination with other information) to determine the appropriate distance at which the model should be rendered or processed.
        Relative TActical Importance is mandatory. It has no default value.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Not Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>7</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="54" symbol="RWID">
      <Name>Runway ID</Name>
      <Description>
        An alphanumeric identifier that, combined with the APID, points to a unique record in the NavData Runway or Helipad dataset
        (i.e., a link to the Runway or Helipad description in the NavData dataset).
        This ID is the value of the field Ident of the Runway or Helipad dataset.
        Note that all of the lights and other features located in list-organized datasets that are associated with the operation of a
        runway or helipad are required to reference a runway or helipad in the NavData dataset;
        the RWID attribute is not required for features unrelated to a runway or helipad.
        Usage Note: Recommended for all Airport Light Points features.
        Failure to appropriately tag airport culture with RWID attribute will result in reduced control of runway-related (or helipad)
        culture by simulator. Optional for Point/Lineal/Areal features, Location Points Features, Environmental Light Point features,
        and Moving Model Location features that are associated with a runway and for which control of the feature is desirable.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>6</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="55" symbol="SCALx">
      <Name>Scaling X-Axis</Name>
      <Description>
        A set of scaling factors, one of the model axis, to be applied to the rendering of model geometry by the client-device.
        A value of 1.0 instructs the client-devices to use the model as-is.
        The physical dimension of models processed by client-device should approach zero, as SCALing tends to zero.
        The value of SCALing should also be accounted for by client-devices (in combination with other information) to determine
        the appropriate distance at which the model should be paged-in, rendered or processed. All three SCALing factors are optional.
        Values of zero and negative values are not permitted.
        Usage Note: Optional; defaults to a value of 1.0 if SCALx, SCALy, or SCALz is missing.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>3.5</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>1000</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>

    <Attribute code="56" symbol="SCALy">
      <Name>Scaling Y-Axis</Name>
      <Description>
        Scale factor to apply to the Y-axis of the model. See SCALx for a detailed description.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>3.5</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>1000</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="57" symbol="SCALz">
      <Name>Scaling Z-Axis</Name>
      <Description>
        Scale factor to apply to the Z-axis of the model. See SCALx for a detailed description.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>3.5</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>1000</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="58" symbol="SJID">
      <Name>Start Junction ID</Name>
      <Description>
        Unique Identification Number that is used to virtually connect the start point of a lineal to another point, lineal or areal feature.
        Lineal features stored in the same shape file having the same SJID or EJID are connected.
        Lineal features stored in different shape files having the same SJID or EJID as the JID listed in the corresponding tile 2D relationship file (*.dbf) are connected.
        Usage Note: Mandatory for all features belonging to Topological Network Datasets.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Not Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="59" symbol="SRD">
      <Name>Surface Roughness Description</Name>
      <Description>
        Describes the condition of the surface materials that may be used for mobility prediction, construction material, and landing sites.
        Enumeration per Table 5-33: Surface Roughness Enumeration Values.
        Usage Note: Recommended for Areal features.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="60" symbol="SSC">
      <Name>Structure Shape Category</Name>
      <Description>
        Describes the Geometric form, appearance, or configuration of the feature.
        Enumeration per Table 5-34: Structure Shape Category Enumeration Values
        Usage Note: Recommended for Point features, and all Network Lineal/Areal Figure Points features.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>

    <Attribute code="61" symbol="SSR">
      <Name>Structure Shape of Roof</Name>
      <Description>
        Describes the roof shape.
        Enumeration per Table 5-35: Structure Shape of Roof Enumeration Values
        Usage Note: Recommended for Point features, and all Network Lineal/Areal Point Figures.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="62" symbol="TRF">
      <Name>Traffic Flow</Name>
      <Description>
        Encodes the general destination of traffic.
        Usage Note: Recommended on all Network Lineal (except PowerLines) features. When absent, client-devices default to a value of 4 (two-way).
        Default: 004 (for RoadNetwork lineal features), 003 (for RailRoadNetwork lineal features)
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="63" symbol="TXID">
      <Name>Taxiway ID</Name>
      <Description>
        A unique alphanumeric identifier (for the airport in question).
        Usage Note: Recommended usage and Optional usages are per table Table 5-37: Allocation of CDB Attributes to Datasets.
        Failure to appropriately tag airport culture with TXID attribute will result in reduced control of taxiway-related culture by a simulation device.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Text</Type>
        <Length>6</Length>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="64" symbol="USP">
      <Name>Urban Street Pattern</Name>
      <Description>
        Describes the predominant geometric configuration of streets found within the delineated area of the feature.
        Enumeration per Table 5-36: Urban Street Pattern Enumeration Values.
        Usage Note: Recommended for Areal features.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="65" symbol="VEAI">
      <Name>Vendor Extended Attribute Index</Name>
      <Description>
        An index that points to a row entry of a VendorExtended Attribution file for the current dataset.
        This entry permits users to store an index to a link list set of Vendor-specific attributes.
        CDB-compliant devices are not mandated to read and interpret this field.
        Usage of this attribution is not portable to other simulators because it falls outside of the documented CDB attribution scheme.
        The Vendor Extended Attribution file should be located in the same directory as the instance-level attribution file.
        An empty VEAI attribute is allowed. Note that the first entry in the Vendor Extended Attribution file has an index of 1.
        Usage Note: Optional. Use when Vendor extended attribution is required. A “blank” or a value of 0 indicates that there are no Vendor Extended attributes.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Not Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Integer</Format>
        <Range>
          <Min>1</Min>
          <Max>999999</Max>
        </Range>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
    <Attribute code="66" symbol="WGP">
      <Name>Width with Greater Than 1 meter Precision</Name>
      <Description>
        For lineal features (such as roads, railways, runways, taxiways), WGP is a measurement of the shorter of two linear axes.
        For a bridge, the width is the measurement perpendicular to the axis between the abutments.
        For powerlines, the width is the distance between the outermost wires.
        Usage Note: Recommended on all Network Lineal features.
      </Description>
      <Level>
        <Instance>Preferred</Instance>
        <Class>Supported</Class>
        <Extended>Supported</Extended>
      </Level>
      <Value>
        <Type>Numeric</Type>
        <Format>Floating-Point</Format>
        <Precision>5.3</Precision>
        <Range interval="Open">
          <Min>0</Min>
          <Max>100000</Max>
        </Range>
        <Unit>1</Unit>
      </Value>
    </Attribute>
    
  </Attributes>
  
  <Units>
  
    <Unit code="1" symbol="m">
      <Name>meter</Name>
      <Description>To measure a length.</Description>
    </Unit>
    
    <Unit code="2" symbol="deg">
      <Name>degree</Name>
      <Description>To mesure an angle.</Description>
    </Unit>
    
    <Unit code="3" symbol="rad">
      <Name>radian</Name>
      <Description>To mesure an angle.</Description>
    </Unit>
    
    <Unit code="4" symbol="kph">
      <Name>Kilometer per hour</Name>
      <Description>To measure a speed.</Description>
    </Unit>
    
    <Unit code="5" symbol="g">
      <Name>gram</Name>
      <Description>To measure a mass.</Description>
    </Unit>
    
    <Unit code="6" symbol="s">
      <Name>second</Name>
      <Description>To measure time.</Description>
    </Unit>
    
    <Unit code="7" symbol="%">
      <Name>Percentage</Name>
      <Description>A value between 0 and 100.</Description>
    </Unit>
    
  </Units>
  
  <Scalers>
  
    <Scaler code="1" symbol="k">
      <Name>kilo</Name>
      <Description>A multiplier: thousand</Description>
      <Multiplier>1000</Multiplier>
    </Scaler>
    
    <Scaler code="2" symbol="m">
      <Name>milli</Name>
      <Description>A divisor: thousandth</Description>
      <Multiplier>0.001</Multiplier>
    </Scaler>
    
  </Scalers>
  
</Vector_Attributes>